This file is for advanced developers only, use at your own risk.  If you can't afford to wait for me to add a new effect/target, and want to add it yourself, use this file to help choose the new id's for your effects/targets (so they don't interfere with the existing ones). Try to use big numbers like 500+ for the same purpose.

for multiplayer, gameobjects id_ingame:
1: player
2: enemy
3:
4*: token cards
5*000*: game zone, number of slot in that game zone



Creature ability triggers:
0: on enter game (doesn't work currently)
1: on activate - players access these through right-click menu

3: when an enemy creature is killed by this one (doesn't work currently)

Example: effect0=1 effect0name="Fireblast" target0=2 trigger0=1 effect0cost=100 param0_0=250
This is a creature's first activated ability (there could be more). It will appear when the player clicks on that creature as a menu button with the name "Fireblast". It costs 100 mana and deals 250 damage to enemy player or creature.

Targets:

		1: target enemy player or creature (for attack)
		2: target enemy player or creature (for spell damage) different targets for attack and spell damage because game rules can differ 
		3: choose a card from your deck (ex. for putting in hand)
		4: two target creatures in game	(can belong to either player)
		5: a target creature (can belong to either player)
		6: a target tapped creature (can belong to either player)
		7: your creature of certain type (target param0 will choose type, for now just one type: hero)
		8: your player or your creature (ex. for buffs)
		9: target friendly creature
		
		10: your player
		11: enemy player
		
		12: all friendly creatures
		13: all creatures
		14: all enemy creatures
		
		15: self (for creature abilities only)
		16: all enemy creatures or heroes
		
		21: a card in hand
		
		30: a target creature with attack <...> or less
		31: a target creature with cost <...> or less
	
		40: a target ally (creature or hero)
		41: a target enemy creature or hero
		
		50: a spell from graveyard (ex. for putting in hand)
		51: a creature from graveyard (ex. for putting in hand)
		
		60: a top card from your deck (ex. for putting in hand)
		99: a creature to grow (as in Pokemon, Wixoss, Vanguard etc) 
		100: reserved, used for multiplayer 
		101: all creatures in a diagonal (doesn't work, was used for LD)
		
		200: random enemy creature (no heroes)
		201: From <target param0> to <target param1> random enemy creatures   
		202: random enemy creature with with cost <...> or less
		
		203: random enemy creature or hero
	
		230: random friendly creature
		
		261: random X creatures
		
		300: random creature in hand
		301: random creature in deck
		302: random creature from grave
		303: random spell from grave
		304: random creature from enemy deck
		
		400: reserved for choose a slot
		
		
		Example: effect0=1 param0_0=600 target0=201 target0param0=3 target0param1=5	
		
		This is the first effect of the spell (it can have more). It deals 600 damage to 3-5 random enemy creatures.
		
		
Effects:
		 0: 	heal  
			
		 1:		 damage 
			
		 2:		draw card(s) NOTARGET
			
		 4: place a card in land zone		
		 5: place a card in your hand 

			
		 6: fight between two creatures
			
		 8: untap target
	
		
			
		 9: kill
			
			
		 10: debuff.  if eot=1, this effect only lasts until end of turn.	// buffs and debuffs are separated for AI to know which effect is to be used on their creatures etc
									
									
									
			
		11: buff  If eot=1, this effect only lasts until end of turn.
									
		buff and debuff types:
									1 - set attack to <param>
									2 - raise/lower attack by <param>
									3 - multiply/divide attack by <param>
									
									7 - set defense to <param>
									8 - raise/lower defense by <param>
									9 - multiply/divide defense by <param>
									
									13 - set crit chance to <param> 
									20 - assign <keyword ability> to a target card									
		
		12: place a new creature (makes a new creature from id) in game under your control NOTARGET
		13: place target creature (from somewhere) in game under your control
		
		15: gain mana NOTARGET
		
		16: swap two cards (not in deck)
		17: add a copy of <target> to deck
		18 : add all copies of <target> from your deck to your hand
		19: move to <target slot>
		
		
		
Example: effect0=11  param0_0=2 target0=5 bufftype0=2 eot=1
This is a buff. You can target either player's creature with it and raise its attack power by 2. It only lasts until the end of turn.		
		
		

Note that activated abilities cause the creature to tap.
		
		